I don't think anyone buys insurance
thinking that they're gonna meet it and
nothing was ever gonna happen to me but
it did and I was very very grateful that
we had this particular product a few
years ago my husband and I decided to
take on an old house and renovate it top
to bottom and our broker introduced us
to this mortgage protection insurance we
decided to purchase it just two years
later I was diagnosed with cancer my
husband and my kids if they had to worry
about money on top of that it just that
would have been really devastating
Manulife just took essentially the
biggest bill we have in our life and
took care of it
having this product just meant the world
and I think it contributed to me getting
through all the really tough treatments
that I had to get through mortgage
brokers that aren't offering this
service I feel are doing their clients a
disservice you never know what's gonna
happen to you the better prepared you
are the better you can face whatever
comes your way